Battle between top popular idols is to start
Classical idols vs New-gen idols
Opening show
Director
Choreographer
Dancer
XIA Zhen
TANG Jun
SDT
[Source: 十年一顾杂货铺]
[Translation: Quadrifolium]
[Timing: Quadrifolium]
[Encoding: Quadrifolium]
Super Leader
XIE Na
HU Hai-quan
Thank you
Welcome. This is Zhejiang TV
the brand-new large-scale in-studio
skill-cultivating programme
Super Idol
The literal translation of the name is "Trumps vs Trumps".
[Sponsor]
[Ad]
I have a question
What's up?
(Wong) Cho-lam, how do you get taller?
Cho-lam
How do you
get taller
You just find it?
Cho-lam is …
He has other work abroad
and can't be back
Busy
Invite Hai-quan to take the place
He asked me on WeChat:
"Cannon" (HU Hai-quan), could you help me for the hosting?
I said: I can take it
But I'm worried
Because I have watched all the previous episodes
He hasn't won for even once
Pitiful
He hasn't won
for even once
In my opinion, he may be thinking
that he just can't bear it
Feared
Better to change a person
it's better to change a person
He lost face here
and left
Dear me
Too much
pressure
Today, the guests coming here
are the top popular idols in two generations
Top popular idols in two generations
They will fight for
the symbol of the top honour –
the identification of the volume of record sales
Identification of the volume of record sales
Fight for
Wonderful shows coming
OK
Now, I'll introduce the top idols in my team
First, they are as young as mine
As young as me
as good-looking as me
As good-looking as me
and have performed on Chunwan (CCTV New Year's Gala)
Have performed on Chunwan
Looking
forward
Let's welcome TFBOYS
Please
Crazy
Passionate
Ears turn
deaf
Popular idols
Youth coming
Battle between top popular idols is to start
Classical idols vs New-gen idols
Manual of Youth (青春修炼手册), TFBOYS, Manual of Youth, 2014
[Rough translation]
Raise your hand, left, right, and move slowly
Manual of Youth
Performer
Director
Choreographer
Dancer
XIA Zhen
SDT
Right, left, the slow move again
May the song makes you happy
Have you fallen in love with me?
Limber up nose, eyes, and ears with me
乖
Be cute or smart, change the styles without stop
The youth contains too many unknowns
Never mind the growing pains
Thank you
Well. Hello
I am
Pinky boy
WANG Jun-kai
(Karry)
the all-in-pink WANG Jun-kai (Karry)
Welcome, WANG Jun-kai (Karry)
Hello. Hello, everyone
In the group, I am
the most quiet prince charming – WANG Yuan (Roy)
Cute boy
WANG Yuan
(Roy)
Cute
Welcome, the charming WANG Yuan (Roy)
好
Hello, everyone. I am
the "gaoleng" boy – YI Yang-qian-xi (Jackson)
"Gaoleng" (高冷), buzzword, originally means "act as an elite and be indifferent to others", but usually simply means "calm and cool".
"Gaoleng" boy
YI Yang-qian-xi
(Jackson)
Our team is titled
"the classical top popular idols"
Classical top popular idols
Attention focused
Classical idol
Selina
Ella
Welcome
Hello
Good evening
I am Selina (Jen)
I am Ella (Chen)
There lacks an "H" in "S.H.E"
Doubting
There lacks
an "H"
So, we added the "H"
Wondering
Who is that "H"?
Who's the "H"?
A charming man
Prince charming
and an excellent idol
Excellent idol
An excellent idol
He's popular in the whole Asia
Popular in Asian
in the whole world, in Hollywood
Popular in the world
Popular in Hollywood
Curious
Who is the idol?
He is definitely the one in everyone's youth
Full of memory
The youth
of one generation
Please applaud and welcome him
Wait and see
Mystery guest about to come
Classical idol
Wang Leehom
Overjoyed
Heroes of Earth
Performer
Director
Choreographer
Dancer
Wang Leehom
XIA Zhen
YANG Chao
SDT
Heroes of Earth (盖世英雄), Wang Leehom (王力宏), Heroes of Earth, 2005
[Rough translation]
The heroes of Earth are coming
The world is my stage
Hello, I am "(Lee)hom"
Revealed
I am that "H"
Leehom, do you find
that the rivals today
are quite different
with you in the ages
Yes
You will combat with them today
What are you thinking about?
I think, this combat is …
a healthy competition
Is it?
I don't think so
Please respect us
A Chinese idiom which means one is much older and more experienced.
Because we had more salt
than the rice they had
A little
scared
The general rule:
In the end of each game
each team rolls a dice
to gain the volume of record sales
The winner rolls the golden dice
the loser the silver dice
The number on the top of the dice
turns to the volume of the round
The sum of the volume …
Welcome
This is Zhejiang TV, the brand-new
large-scale in-studio skill-cultivating programme
Super Idol
I'm SHEN Tao
Ella, to tell you
Classical idols            New-gen idols
He does better in cute actions than you
Wong Cho-lam's team
XIE Na's team
Really?
Defying
Come on. Show me
Skilled
actions
I see your belly
Jiejie
I have more
Both of you are great
This is the first time
someone challenging with cute actions on this stage
But I think you did very very well
Let's speak out our slogan, OK?
OK
TFBOYS and XIE Na
Youth works through the world
Conceited
Heng
And your slogan is …
In the whole world, Selina and Ella are the most popular
HU Hai-quan and Wang Leehom's names appear as homophones.
We all know
that you are all super idols in music
And the following section
is about singing skills
In this section
when you choose a song
that song is also given
a supernatural ability
Singing
With supernatural abilities
Supernatural KTV
[Ad]
The rule of "Supernatural KTV":
Game
Supernatural KTV
Each team should send out its members
and choose a record in turn
Each record carries a song
and contains a supernatural ability
The players
should cope with different situations
and stabilise the voice
After the singing
the system will give the score
The team with higher score
wins the game
Classical idols            New-gen idols
In the first round, I assign it to the three boys
OK?
OK
TFBOYS, go
Supernatural records
TFBOYS set off
No. 1 – 9
Which one do you choose?
From 9 records
Choose one
To make choice
Grab the fate in the hand
One of them is Para Paramita
Para Paramita (菠萝菠萝蜜), XIE Na (谢娜), Para Paramita, 2006
World-class
Para
Paramita
Na jie:
Now I've told you
Chose No. 3
No. 3, …
A good luck on the choice
this is exactly Para Paramita
Really?
Para
Paramita
Not at all!
Not at all
As I've said
each song carries a supernatural ability
Some of the abilities can help you
Good ability
Improves the score
but some …
I can't be sure what will happen here
Bad ability
Please pray for it
Terrible
Ominous
presentiment
Dear me
Scary
Dear me!
The song you chose is …
Perturbed
The song is …
"Song of the Fifth Ring"
Song of the Fifth Ring
That's worse than Para Paramita
Gloating
Worse than my song
Eclipsed
Can we change?
Boys, pray
Song of the Fifth Ring (五环之歌), YUE Yun-peng (岳云鹏) & MC HotDog, Soundtrack of Jian Bing Man (煎饼侠 电影原声), 2015
[Rough translation]
Ah, the Fifth Ring (Road)
You are one ring outer than the Fourth Ring
I drive the car onto the Fifth Ring
It's my path to drive on the Fifth Ring
Ah, the Fifth Ring
You are one ring outer than the Fourth Ring
Getting
better
You are one ring inner than the Sixth Ring
Suddenly
Curtain
open
Who's that
Stunned
Inconceivable
Startled
Petrified
Who is coming?
Helper
YUE Yun-peng
The original
He comes
Surprise
The original
Yes
The original singer comes
You are one ring outer than the Fourth Ring
Ah, the Fifth Ring
You are one ring inner than the Sixth Ring
This is the type of
a strengthened supernatural ability
Lucky
The original singer helps
Because the original would help you
I … I'm very glad
Bashful
With the help of the original
let's take a look at the score of the singing
Please watch
Waiting for the result
Aiyo
Not bad
I think it's not bad
Please
console me
OK
Is it a high score?
The full mark is 150
Joking
The full mark
is 150
It's your turn
They are an ideal couple
Hai-quan's team
Ideal couple set off
Who?
Selina and Leehom
Exclaiming
Pepping
We are the best
Well, No. 6 is Para Paramita
Not resigned
Still
promoting
Is No. 6 Para Paramita?
We choose No. 2
Kidding
We choose
No. 2
This song is
Ruthless
You Are A Song in My Heart
Name of the song
What a coincidence
This is just your song
Complaining
This is
your song
The original
You Are A Song in My Heart
Wang Leehom
You Are A Song in My Heart (你是我心内的一首歌), Wang Leehom (王力宏) & Selina Jen (任家萱), Change Me (改变自己), 2007
[Rough translation]
You are a song in my heart
Together
A flower blooms in my mind
You are a song in my life
My longing forms a river
The song bears in my heart
Suddenly
Curtain
open again
Dear me
This time
Who's coming …?
Don't just be a passer-by
Burst into laughter
Leave a song in my life
Knows nothing
No matter …
Unhappy
Beautiful scene broken at once
Who are you?
This guest is too weak
Right
How I wish to ask
Helper
Hank Chen
Toasted
Toasted, that's deducting
That would make a deduction
if you rose any favour on me
Successfully
Keeps away from all the tones
Cannot bear
Very angry
Could you please be serious?
How I wish to ask
if you rose any favour on me
Out of tune all along
KTV terminator
Loathing
Leave a song in my life
No matter what the result will be
Big hindrance
Go away
Mister, …
Can we remake this part?
Can we pretend it didn't happen?
Can we?
But this is the supernatural ability of this song
Innocent
Have I done
anyting wrong?
Can we change a card?
Unwilling
Raging to the utmost
Can we?
Wait
I haven't introduced myself
Poor
guy
How are you?
Go back
Under attack
Ungrateful
teammate
I …
No
We will remake this part
We will remake, remake …
The singers, please talk about
this song
and the supernatural ability it carries
What do you think?
Whammy
In chorus
One word
Whammy
Tacit word
The same thought
makes a team
What?
The guest of our team
Mutual assessment
has some words for this guest
Hearing
Xiao Yue-yue, what are your words?
I think …
Just look at the score, OK?
No comment
Just look
at the score
What is their score?
Please watch
With the disservice
What is their score?
Inconceivable
Favoured from Lady Luck
Round 1
Hai-quan's team
XIE Na's team
You are leading at present
88 – 76
In this round
Hai-quan's team wins
You see
Well done
OK. Thank you, Hank
Wait
In the next round
we'll win back
for the supernatural ability
of this song
Come on. Please get back to your seats
You are leading at present
Well
I will assign the task
Next
I will still assign it to …
Whom?
To turn the tables
Get to stage to catch the eyes
It cannot be lagged behind
To take the score back
Yes
OK
Please choose a record
No. 5
Why do you choose this one?
Choose No. 5
Because No. 6 is Para Paramita
No one wants to …
All right. We choose No. 6
No. 6
Please don't expose it
No, …
Live your life on your own
No. 5?
Grateful
Na jie
gives a way out
Record No. 5 carries the song …
What's the surprise this time?
Three Days and Nights
A quick-paced song, …
Out of
the blue
Three Days and Nights (三天三夜), A-mei (张惠妹, Kulilay Amit), Can I Huge You? My Love (我可以抱你吗? 爱人), 1999
[Rough translation]
For three days and nights, in the midnight
Don't stop your dance moves
No tired at all
I have danced for three days and nights
At this moment, even soda water can make me drunk
I will not get tired at all
I can dance for three more days and nights
Wire descending
No, …
What is the supernatural ability?
What's happening?
What's up?
No
Looking up
Dear me
Wire work on the stage
It can't be
Mamma mia
Soar at once
With no sign
Completely stunned
Rise again
Dolphin's voice
Ah!
Dumbfounded
Three days and nights
Yelling with all the strength
For three days and nights, in the midnight
Don't stop your dance moves
I float in the music
Soar
For three days and nights, in the midnight
Wide-eyed
So scary
I sweat all over
This is the first time I witnessed
Sing with you and make you fly
Adapted from a cyber phrase.
Live
Sing with you
and make you fly
The supernatural ability of this song
in my opinion
is to squeeze out the high pitch
It's normal in the beginning …
"For three days and nights …"
Dolphin's voice
Ah!
Next, let's take a look
that with the supernatural ability of wiring
the score of TFBOYS is …
The score of XIE Na's team is …
Good
Not bad
We have players not performed yet
Yes
Ella
Sends out
She is the mic controller
Really
Real Mic Controller
It's too lonely for her
I send another prince charming
Not modest
at all
That is me
A prince?
Remember not to choose No. 6
Unwritten rule
Keep away from No. 6
Of course not
Right
Ella, … No. 6
It's Para Paramita
New Para Paramita
I've made up …
Shirking
Never choose it
It's too late
Is it?
I can hold on
You will be
regretful
No. 7
is a classic song
Love Is Like the Tide
Love Is Like the Tide (爱如潮水), Jeff Chang (张信哲), Worrying (心事), 1993
[Rough translation]
My love is like the tide
The tide pushes me to you
and follows closely
爱如潮水 它将你我包围
The tide surrounds you and me
I'm quite adept at
such old songs
Old song
My strength
Please look forward to
the supernatural ability of this song
Wondering
Pleasant
or frightened?
What's that?
It seems horrible
Mic with strong airflow
Familiar prop
Shock
Hidden air nozzle
Happy New Year
Cannot believe it
Ha?
Big challenge
Please be seated
As we are in love, make it with no regret
Affectionate
No matter how hard it is, I can bear them all
Intoxicated
How nice
My love is like the tide
Turns
pale
Here it comes, …
My love is like the tide
The tide pushes me to you
and follows closely
The tide surrounds you and me
Grit the teeth
Singing in strong wind
Oh, yeah
Point to the mouth
Medium
mode
I don't want to see you being drunken in the night
Suddenly
Here comes
men in black
don't want other men to see your enchantment
Firmly
pinned
Bro
That's
too much
The men in black is too cruel
You should know …
Curious
Promise me not to wander in the night from now on
Ella's face is so funny
It's so funny, so funny
Do you know that makes my heart broken
Xiao Yue-yue
It's so funny
My heart is broken
It's a hard task
Let's take a look at
what score do they get
[Sponsor] witnesses the trump with you
The score of Hai-quan's team is …
Hai-quan's
team
XIE Na's
Round 1
Round 2
In this round
Hai-quan's team wins
Gratify
Well, let's welcome the Super Girl
to take the golden and silver dices here
Please
Super dices
Silver dice for this team
Golden for that
Here comes the dice
[Ad]
The silver dice rolls first, OK?
1 2 Go
The volume of XIE Na's team is …
XIE Na's team
Round 1
The second high
My turn, …
OK. Your team
Roll higher
The volume of Hai-quan's team is …
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Round 1
Good
Being happy is the most important, right?
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Current situation
Hai-quan's team leads
Yes
Yes. Be happy
They are consoling themselves
Pitying
They are
consoling themselves
1 2 3
TFBOYS, Xiao Yue-yue, and XIE Na
Youth works through the world
Aggressive
Stand to win
HU Hai-quan and Hank Chen's names appear as homophones.
In the whole world, Selina, Ella, and Leehom
stand to win
Aggressive
Stand to win
To be an outstanding
all-round idol
you should have the ability of imitating
The next section
is to test this aspect
Let's get to "Imitate Idols"
Actually, for
every one who will
stand and perform
on this stage
I think, this is
a very difficult challenge
As what I've told you
the popular idols of two different generation
will pair with each other
and show us
their favourite songs
to show us a different view
It's a challenge
it makes us anticipated
Imitate Idols
Who is the king of imitation?
What sparks between the idols?
In this section, the idols
will cooperate
to make imitations
Each pair will choose a song
for the performance
This section is an interaction
it doesn't make scores
Now
Please wait for
the moment the screen opens
Who are in the first pair?
Please wait
Pair 1
YI Yang-qian-xi & Ella Chen
YI Yang-qian-xi            Ella Chen
XIE Na's team
YI Yang-qian-xi
(Jackson)
Hai-quan's team
Ella Chen
Cool
Domineering
Qian-xi (Jackson), …
Bang Bang Bang (뱅뱅뱅), Big Bang (빅뱅), A, 2015
Performer
Original singer
Director
Choreography
Dance
Ella & YI Yang-qian-xi
XIA Zhen
SDT
Banging on
Imposing show
Hot dance
The air is banging
It's banging
So cool
A huge bang
Did you have to?
Yes
Cool
Ella
It's so cool
Your lips turned pale
Lips turned pale
White?
Awkward
You find it
Please take a breath
Take a breath
I'd like to talk to Qian-xi (Jackson) first
How do feel about
the cooperation with Ella?
It's getting high
Because
this is a song of the idols I worship
That makes it higher
Exciting show
Right
The stage was banging
Do you find that
this match
is very suitable
Yes
They are banging
And …
Next …
we can wait for the next pair
Yes
I can't wait
Who are in the next pair?
Please be seated
Go, …
Who are in the next pair
for the challenge?
[Ad]
Please watch
Come on
Surprised
What's that?
Expecting
[Sponsors]
Surprised
What's that?
Expecting
WANG Yuan               Selina Jen
Pair 2
WANG Yuan & Selina Jen
Cute
So cute
Pure and cute
A Chick Bibi (小鸡哔哔), adapted from El Pollito Pio (a spanish song in Italy).
[Rough translation]
Look. There is a chick oh
A chick bibi yo
A Chich Bibi
Performer
Director
Choreographer
Dancer
Selina & WANG Yuan
XIA Zhen
SDT
A chick bibibibi yo
Look. There is a pigeon oh
A pigeon lululu (coo)
A turkey dududu
A rooster wowowo (cock-a-doodle-doo)
A hen gegege (cluck)
A chick bibi yo
A chick bibibibi yo
Look. There is a bull oh
A bull moo
A cow moh
羊
A sheep mie (baa)
A goat meh (baa)
A puppy bowwow-wow
A kitty Meow-ow-ow
A pigeon lululu (coo)
A turkey dududu
A rooster o-o-o (cock-a-doodle-doo)
A hen gegege (cluck)
A chick bibi yo
A chick bibibibi yo
Look. There is a tractor yo
A tractor ong (drone)
A chick o-o-o (cock-a-doodle-doo)
Is that cute?
Yes, so cute
We have
"A Chick Bibi" three cute poses
OK
Come on, …
Three cute poses
[Ad]
So cute
It's very …
WANG Yuan (Roy), please tell us
what is the key point of the dance?
The key point?
I think the key point is this
Wiggle
A chick bibi
So cute
Right, …
这个
Let's do it together
Together, …
Follow him
OK. Please
Look. There is a chick yo
A chick bibi yo
Watching carefully
With
ease
A chick bibibibi yo
Look. There is a pigeon oh
Stiff
A pigeon lululu (coo)
A turkey dududu
A rooster wowowo (cock-a-doodle-doo)
Hai-quan gradually keeps up
A hen gegege (cluck)
A chick bibi yo
A chick bibibibi yo
Good
Relieved
It's
finally over
So cute
During this imitation
I think the most awkward one is "Cannon"
I …
In this age
Grieved
Imitating a chick
I feel like being in the wrong place
Well
Who are in the next pair
for the challenge?
Come on
WANG Jun-kai               Wang Leehom
XIE Na's team
WANG Jun-kai's solo
BGM: Hood Go Crazy, Tech N9ne & 2 Chainz & B.o.B, Special Effects, 2015
Where's Leehom ge?
Suddenly found
Where's he?
Leehom ge, where are you?
I'm here
Wang Leehom
Where?
What's happening?
What's that?
Wang Leehom with a broom
Leehom
Becomes
a guitar
Prince of guitar showing charm
Guitar solo
Original
Copied
Flung here
Good household article
Improvised performance
A sorcerer, …
Potion of
Forgetfulness?
Infatuated
How charming
Smart
Imitating posture
The heavenly king appears
Cool
Thank you
Andy Lau
Potion of Forgetfulness
Potion of Forgetfulness (忘情水), Andy Lau (刘德华), Potion of Forgetfulness, 1994
[Rough translation]
I was chasing dream when I was young
Focused on flying higher and further
The Heavenly King
I have walked around numerous mountains and rivers
This road cannot be pulled back
When I turned back, the love was away
Appealing
I cannot help but let it go
And I got to know that among all the feelings
Regret hurts the deepest
The Heavenly King
Stunned
Critical props come
Potion of Forgetfulness
Ah
Give me the Potion of Forgetfulness
for a night without tears
Drink up
in one breath
The whole sincere heart and soul
exposes to wind and rain
The love payed gets nothing back
How thirsty
Give me the Potion of Forgetfulness
for a life without sorrow
More water?
Though I get drunk
One more drink
though my heart's broken
Why are you performing drinking?
I am living without tears
Though I get drunk
Sincere
Earnest
though my heart's broken
I am living without tears
Great
We didn't expect that on the glass
So cool
it labeled
"Potion of Forgetfulness"
Can I drink (the potion)?
Great
Both of you found
the sense of a Heavenly King
Especially the pointing to the audience
I think …
Repeat
at once
Cool
Leehom is good at imitating
Really?
Do you know who's the most similar person
he imitates?
Who?
That's me
Is that true?
Cannot believe it
Leehom imitates Hank Chen
Hank Chen. Really
Leehom, please show us
Classical idols            New-gen idols
He imitates me …
We can imitate
each other
I imitate him
Get into play
at once
What is "imitating each other"?
That's it
Double Hanks
I am …
I am Hank Chen
Quite similar
Hello. Thank you
Is it funny?
Naughty
Just can't stop it
Very similar
Alike in sense
Turned
shy
We have another show waiting in the back
Another show?
Please be seated first
and greet him
Who's waiting?
The last one?
A super star
Dear friends
At this moment
you must have found there's a person left
Well
The next show is not from Xiao Yue-yue
but another super star
Super                      star
Please welcome
Welcome
Xiao Yue-yue
What a long …
Let's welcome Xiao Yue-yue
Heroes of Earth
Xiao Yue-yue
Of Xiao Yue-yue
What is the costume?
Oh, my god
Xiao Yue-yue
Dazzling
Fat Wang Leehom
Oh, my god
Wandering
mind
Limp legs, …
Original
Copied
Standard equip
Guitar in hand
The monkeys are coming
Stiff
Change Me
Performer
Original singer
Director
Choreographer
Dancer
YUE Yun-peng
Wang Leehom
XIA Zhen
LI Yu-xi
SDT
It seems he's very angry
Change Me (改变自己), Wang Leehom (王力宏), Change Me, 2007
[Rough translation]
I looked at myself in the mirror after getting up
Exactly this
feeling
and found my hair turned a little "kuso"
A tiny change may lead to a huge difference
Our strength can change the whole world
I can change the whole world, change myself
remove estrangement, reverse passiveness
Strive all the time, never give up
and I can change the whole world, change myself
Dear me
Please
take my guitar
Give me the guitar
Chasing
The monkeys
Xiao Yue-yue left away
Left the audience confused
What are you doing?
Get back
Solo, …
Back on track
Beautiful
Performer
Original Singer
Director
Choreographer
Dancer
YUE Yun-peng
Wang Leehom
XIA Zhen
LI Yu-xi
SDT
Beautiful (美), Wang Leehom (王力宏), The 18 Martial Arts (十八般武艺), 2010
You are beautiful, you are charming
You are beautiful, …
Dancer changed
Awkward
You are beautiful, …
What should I do?
You are charming, you are beautiful, …
He turns shy
You are beautiful, you are charming
Keep singing
Braced up
Xiao Yue-yue starts to sing
You are beautiful, …
He's restraining
That's too affected
Xiao Yue-yue, you win
Finally
it ended
Why did you turn shy, Xiao Yue-yue?
Well
In my view
in his performance
one of the highlight
is chasing the guitar
Actually
It's quite good in the beginning
I'm not embarrassed with a guitar
you know?
Suddenly …
he said
you should give me the guitar
and sing Beautiful on your own
I agreed
I gave him
but found
it's too embarrassed
Pass me the costume for a while
I'd like to put it on
What are you
going to do?
Special
hair
That hair
suits you very well
What do you mean?
Xiao Yue-yue
Mamma mia
Shy
Burst All Out, OK?
Burst All Out (火力全开), Wang Leehom (王力宏), Burst All Out, 2011
Burst All Out
Hank Chen imitates Wang Leehom
Burst All Out?
Burst All Out
Vivid moves
Exhausted
Do you need a chair for a rest?
I need a chair
and water
Leehom, they are imitating you
Can you imitate others?
Right
That's right. Can you?
Show us
Perturbed
"Perturbed"(忐忑) is an experimental work with no lyrics, sung by vocalist GONG Lin-na(龚琳娜), composed by her spouse Robert Zollitsch(老锣).
Comes easy
GONG Lin-na's Perturbed
Can you?
Perturbed from Leehom
Go for it
Have a try
Music, …
I'll try
Good
Anything happened?
Great
Too crazy
Great, …
Today
having the oppotunity
to watch such a show from Leehom
I'm pleased
That's right
The next section
is a test of composure on stage
The following section
is called
"Stroke of Fate"
Stroke of Fate
[Ad]
The rule of "Stroke of Fate":
Game
Stroke of Fate
Two players from both teams
plays rock-paper-scissors
The winner
knock the rival's head with a gourd ladle
The loser defend with a pot cover
A successful knock makes 1 point
A successful escape makes 1 point
The team with higher score win
Classical idols            New-gen idols
As to the ladle
Before the game
Players studying the prop
you should make it broken
knock fast
and it won't ache
Do not imitate
It's very crisp
It's totally dry
It's crisp
so, it's easily broken
Please don't imitate
It doesn't ache. Really
Don't worry
Look
I can eat it
Ah
Edible?
Na-na, are you hungry?
Naïve
Are you hungry?
She's not eating
That's naughty
Now we may start the game
Classical idols            New-gen idols
The two players
Round 1
WANG Jun-kai vs Wang Leehom
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
please claim your strength to your rival
to rout him in mentality
Wait
I have words
He is a father of two children
Claiming
Got it?
Counterattack
He is a child
Haha …
Please be ready
Well
Rock-paper-scissors
1st throw
Wang Leehom wins
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Escaped
Skipped
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Nervous
Reluctant
Well, one more time
Rock-paper-scissors
Got a chance but hesitated
Slight touch
No one gets 1 point
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Rock-paper-scissors
Halted
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Too restrained
Na-na can't stand it anymore
You respond so fast
You are …
No matter win or lose
they are just making a pose
don't knock at all
Too hard
to make it
Till now
Intact ladle
Please be ready
Rock-paper-scissors
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Will Leehom make it?
Fly
Only the handle
It cracked
You smashed it into pieces
Till now
no one gets the first point
Because no one get knocked
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Leehom is very cared about Xiao-kai (Karry)
Full of love
They made it 0 – 0
Let's make it fiercer
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Round 2
YUE Yun-peng vs Hank Chen
Please be ready
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 1
Hank Chen wins
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Yue-yue
Rooted to the spot
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Your right hand
didn't even moved a little
I have nothing
to say
Well, the next
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 2
YUE Yun-peng wins
My turn
Hesitating
In a flurry
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
What
happened
Still unaware
Immersed in the illusion
He made … the defense
Finally reacted
The rival made the defense
Totally
frustrated
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Well, the next
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 3
YUE Yun-peng wins
Thunder-like speed
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Made it?
No
Still no?
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
At the moment he knocked
Flown ladle
A successful escape
It hit on the edge of the cover
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Till now, Hank leads with 1 – 0
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 4
Picked up at the same time
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
This time
Will Xiao Yue-yue succeed?
Breathe
in relief
Why is the fate
teasing me
Still 1 – 0?
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Still 1 – 0
The last time
Yes, the last time
Rock-paper-
Xiao Yue-yue's final chance
Will he turn the tables
scissors
DRAW
Expecting
too early
Rock-paper-scissors
Restart
Who will win the deciding set?
Throw 5
Hank Chen wins
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Run away
at once
It's 2 – 0
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Well, the leaders, please assign
The next one
Leave it to me, …
Who? …
I, …
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Ella versus whom?
Round 3
WANG Yuan vs Ella Chen
Xiao-yuan (Roy)
OK. Ella versus Xiao-yuan (Roy)
Ready?
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 1
Ella Chen wins
Hit out
Nice defence
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Momentum is important at any time
Momentum is important
Rock-paper-scissors
Pins the cover
Struck
with panic
Ladle?
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Once more
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 3
WANG Yuan wins
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Hooray
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 4
Ella Chen wins
Go
Highly raised, softly laid
Made it
It's on the cover
She made it
Honest
You are …
You are so honest
We admit what is the truth
You made it
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Give me five
Friendship comes before championship
Suddenly changed
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 5
Ella Chen wins
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Rock-paper-scissors
Start at once
Ella hurries with no stop
No …
Props are
not ready
No ladle
Wait
See?
They are both aggressive
Yes, aggressive
Once more
Rock-paper-
[Sponsors]
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Rock-paper-
Strongers' duel
Collision between aggressors
scissors
Throw 6
Ella Chen wins
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Knocking herself
Picks up the ladle at once
and knocks at the head
Ella's fully muddled
I don't concede
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
I'm too excited
I'm too eager for a win
Once more
Jiejie in high morale
Didi in high tension
Rock-paper-scissors
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Throw 7
WANG Yuan wins
In top speed
Hai-quan's team retreats further
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Classical idols            New-gen idols
All right, …
Round 4
XIE Na vs HU Hai-quan
Come on, …
Fashionable
The most fashionable
Leader
Doubting
Stunned by the hair
What are you doing?
What's your tactic?
To make a buffer
I don't borrow anything
It's on my body
In the last round
Tied up during spectating
Here
Embarrassed
Hard to knock
Na jie, …
Advising
Use
honey trap
Honey trap
I don't have
How to trap with this figure?
Honey trap?
Leader, …
Your battle is very important
We can't lose
That's right
Now the critical moment
Leaders, please claim your strength to your rival
You can't even see my moves
This figure
scares
This figure is fierce enough
In Running Man (Chinese ver.)
Hai-quan defeated Cholam
Rock-paper-scissors
and beat Bao-qiang easily
scissors
Too hard to pick it up
Who's the next?
Will the invincible winner
be the victor this time?
Bring it on
The final battle between two leaders
Concentrated
Nervous
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Rock-paper-scissors
Sharp eyes and agile hand
Leader
How can it be that fast?
Unique skill
Stretch on the left
Pick up on the right
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
You can't even see my moves
"Cannon" acts well
Disappeared from the camera
The ambition gets to the end
Na-na
Na-na, where are you?
In martial art, being fast can never be broken
[Ad]
Just wait and see
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Rock-paper-scissors
Posthaste
sheltering
Swift response
Fast sheltering
Aiya, our leader is also very fast
Morale
agitated
Come on
OK. Come on, …
Rock-paper-scissors
Throw 3
Draw
To the ladle
To the cover
Retracts
After the draw
Both flustered
Wait, …
Take it easy, …
Not bad
Calm down
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Before the game ends
they have threatened themselves to death
How do you become leaders?
You are too cowardly
Get ready
Rock-paper-scissors
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Suddenly changed
What's happening?
Para Paramita
Take me away, take me away
Just dance
Finally, this song sounds
Specially prepared   Do not imitate
Fix the hair
Perfect shelter for the knock
OK. Please be ready
Come on
The last round
The last throw
Who will win?
Rock-paper-scissors
Straight to the point
Hai-quan
I'm sorry
Concede the defeat
I'm … Wait
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
In this section, the winner is Na-na's team
Stroke of Fate
XIE Na's team wins
Well
Let's welcome the Super Girl
to take the dices here
Time time, the silver dice for that side
Thank you
OK
I roll
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Round 1
Round 2
Go
OK. Roll
This side
Give them a chance (to catch up)
As Na-na's team wins
Na-na could make
the punishment here
to order the rivals
Wow
Ah
Punishment?
It's simple
What's that?
To change the profile image on (Sina) Weibo
Change it to the photo of your member
Yes
When the programme broadcasts
Wow
OK
I change it to WANG Yuan(Roy)'s
WANG Yuan(Roy)'s
I change it to Qian-xi(Jackson)'s
Right
And you change it to Jun-kai(Karry)'s
Yours
To Jun-kai(Karry)'s
And I change it to Xiao Yue-yue's
OK. To mine
Take it one by one
Grimace
Qian-xi (Jackson)
That's too cute
As the guests on this stage
are all top popular idols
In the next section
please use your voice
to pay your respects to masterworks of each other
But this section is more difficult
On this stage, you should
perform the song of the idols of the other team
Now, let's get to the section
"Respect and Inheritance"
Please welcome TFBOYS
for Wang Leehom's Heart Beat
Wang Leehom
Heart Beat
Heart Beat (心跳), Wang Leehom (王力宏), Heart Beat, 2008
[Rough translation]
Want to quarrel with me
I'm not that dull
Apology is too hard
I'm not that smart
How I wish to get back
to the initial point
Heart Beat + Dance Show
Performer
Stage Director
Music Director
Choreographer
Arranger
Dance
XIA Zhen
LOU En-qi
ZHU Min
XU Lin
SDT
Want to quarrel with me
I'm not that dull
Apology is too hard
I'm not that smart
How I wish to get back
to the initial point
You are crying again
but I can't console you
I am shaking the head again
that I'm a little regretful
The progress of love
is hard to turn back
but cannot walk on
But I can hardly
control myself
How many question marks
can be filled between the two hearts?
How many tears have we shed?
Your eyes are so beautiful
It takes my heart beat away
Your tenderness is so close
Turn the time back to the beginning
Can I have one more second?
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Some day
you may find
the happiness lingering in the memory
Great
Disappeared
Did they travel?
Where did they go?
Time travel?
The little three leaning out slowly
Persian Cat
Performer
Stage Director
Music Director
Choreographer
Arranger
Dance
XIA Zhen
LOU En-qi
ZHU Min
XU Lin
SDT
Come on
Persian Cat
ฅ(>ω<)
Persian Cat (波斯猫), S.H.E, Magical Journey(奇幻旅程), 2004
[Rough translation]
Squint the eyes to a line
stand on tiptoes softly
The tiles on the roof
form his keyboard
Step by step, little by little
drifting on the edge of love
Appears at will
disappears at will
Sleeps for the whole day at will
ignores anyone at will
Doesn't call back, doesn't get online
doesn't argue with anyone at all
ฅ(>ω<)
Falling in love with him is dangerous
Not being in love makes one longing
He's always lukewarm or aloof
looming or gleaming
Sometimes silent and indifferent
sometimes tender and bashful
No one can be
the master of his love
Lingering when getting close
Absent-minded when leaving away
He's zealous or apathy
intimate or alienated
He can be unchanged
he can be variable
But he will never
make any change for you
Persian cat
is squinting his eyes
is standing on his tiptoes
Persian cat
is guarding his love
But in a trice
he disappears
Disappears in a trice
Na …
ฅ(>ω<)
Young and cute
The original singers are sitting there
This is quite a tense moment
Yes
Very nervous
Let's listen to Leehom's assessment
about Heart Beat
It has their own taste
Yes
and it's cool
with their body moves
This is a ballad
Yes
but it possesses a sense of dance music
of clear rhythm
I like it
So, thank you for your respect
So cute
And they are diligent
Because their …
their costumes
the surroundings
and the dance moves
are exactly the same as ours
It seems that they made great efforts on it
Choosing these songs
is to pay respect to the seniors
To receive their praise
may also make your heart
contented very much
Please applaud
the adorable TFBOYS
Please welcome Wang Leehom and Ella for Manual of Youth
Manual of Youth + Beautiful
Performer
Stage Director
Music Director
Wang Leehom & Ella
XIA Zhen
LOU En-qi
Manual of Youth (青春修炼手册), TFBOYS, Manual of Youth, 2014
[Rough translation]
Raise your hand, left, right
and move slowly
Right, left
the slow move again
Manual of Youth
Polish my shoes, put on my suit
wear the diamond of my dream
My courage is fully charged
Be proud to reach every place
The sun in the sky
enlightens me
for my confidence
The centre of the stage
is brilliant with me
shines bright with me
Raise your hand, left, right
and move slowly
Right, left
the slow move again
May the song makes you happy
Have you
fallen in love with me?
Yes
Limber up nose, eyes
and ears with me
Be cute or smart
change the styles without stop
The youth contains
too many unknowns
never mind the growing pains
Beautiful (美), Wang Leehom (王力宏), The 18 Martial Arts (十八般武艺), 2010
You are beautiful
You are charming
You are beautiful, …
You are beautiful
All the guests, please come to the stage
When the classical songs were sung on this stage
The cute boys sitting there
may be touched, right?
As what you've said
When you first hear
these familiar songs along the streets
you are very young
What do you feel like?
I feel very honoured
[Ad]
that they sang our song
As you see it
through this section
the artists of two generation
via the respects in this way
on this stage
The commemoration of the past
or the expectation of the future
during the complex of inheritance
in music
it pervades on this stage
Actually, for me, the biggest feeling today
is that being on this stage
is our honour
that we can be the memory
of the youth of some generation
This is a very happy feeling
And, through our music
through our love of the work
to spread a lot of positive energy
to the fans who like us
This is the biggest meaning
of being an idol
Yes
So, seeing the power of the new generation
in music growing
they are feeling very happy
We know
that from their debut
so many years passed
they are using their dedication
endeavour and positive energy
to influence
every fan all the time
Yes
You debuted at a very young age
At this moment
what would you say to your fans?
I'm very grateful
Since we are …
not skilled or experienced
they have liked us
and supported us
Till now, it's …
actually over two years
I'm very grateful to them
Be grateful
He made a good point
And, as Hank's pet phrase, "be grateful"
It's not easy to be grateful
That's great
In my view
the reason that they are so popular
that they gained so many support
lies in that they remain the pure
and simple heart
I think they will always
be pure and sincere
and be cute like angels
On this stage
No matter the glorious seniors
or the new power
that changes our views
they are using their dedication
and positive energy
using their music to bring happiness to everyone
Please applaud all of them
Fine
Thank you
You are excellent
Fighting, …
After the previous section
do you have enough energy to cope with
the coming test about physical strength?
The next section
is called "Battle For Candy"
Battle For Candy
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Welcome back to the [Ad]
"Battle For Candy"
As this is about candy
every player
gets back to the cutest babyhood
Innocent
Back to the cute babyhood
Let's welcome them
Big babies come in
Moe moe
Babyhood
Welcome, the ten cute babies
So cute
The rule of "Battle For Candy":
[Ad]
Game
Battle For Candy
All the members join the game
After the game starts
all the players dance with the music
When the emcee says "start"
a device ejects the candies out
During the set time
the two teams strive for the red candies
Each player can only hold one candy
The player with no candy
or the two players holding the same candy
are out
Each round sifts some players out
until the last player remains
and the team wins
Classical idols            New-gen idols
OK
All the players, please be ready
With the music
please enjoy your warming up
During waiting
Dance with the music
Come on
Time start
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Candies eject
Dash up in a crowd
Players without candies are …
You already have one
WANG Jun-kai
locates the target, hits out quickly
Entangled
Seized the time
Karry pulled the candy out
Successful block
A screech
Ah
Curious
What happened?
Hiding aside
Protecting the candy
All in vain
Leehom snatched the candy
Happy
Leave at once
Leehom took away WANG Yuan(Roy)'s
Sacrificing
Xiao Yue-yue give the candy to Roy
Holding tight
Thank you
Now, only Yue-yue
Franticly
Finding a target
don't have a candy
He locates a target
Ready? The countdown
Lonely
Selina
holding a candy
Decided the prey
Don't take mine
TIME'S UP
Xiao Yue-yue is out
Snatch failed
I'm out of breath
Strength
sapped
It's quite tiring
Gasping
It's very tiring
Very much
Fighting
OK
The next round is crueller
Because this time, there are
only 7 red candies
Red candies
Only seven
This round
Sifts
two
This round sifts two players out
9 players
7 candies
I'm watching you
Declaring
war
I'm waiting
Come on
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Time …
Go away
You go away
Don't touch
Start
Candies eject
Snatch starts
Karry
Ella
Roy
Slipped
Seize the chance
Now it's mine
Confused empty-handed
Perplexed
Good chance
Staying alone
Heihei
I could survive
Na-na is attacking Selina
Tie into
the target
Don't take mine
Give me
Why do you always aimed at me
How dare you attack my sister?
In instinct
Ella bolsters up
Powerful
Touching
Ella fighting
Sisters of the same mind
the sharpness cuts through the metal
Adapted from I Ching (易经, also known as Classic of Changes or Book of Changes).
On the other side …
From the beginning …
Xiao Yue-yue wants to help
Hank haven't touched a candy yet
Give me, …
Take it
TIME'S UP
In this round, Ella and Hank
Crisis of Hai-quan's team
Two players out
don't have candies
No
What a pity
Hank and Ella are out
I want
to cry
OK
Now the players in the field are 3 – 4
XIE Na's team slightly dominates
But now
in the ejector
there are only 5 red candies
Ah?
In this round, 7 players for 5 candies
Two players will be out
7 players
5 candies
Fighting
Go for it
Fight for the victory
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Please be ready
Box out
Box out first
Look out for XIE Na
Advising
Look out
for XIE Na
We
know that
Eject
Candies eject
Leehom
Karry
Hai-quan
Jackson
No one takes the last candy
XIE Na
In a hurry
Escaped
Take a breath
Take a look at
the situation
In the field
The three boys are chased
Calm
Roy is not carrying a candy
Thinking
What should
I do?
Attack XIE Na
XIE Na
Break point
Attack XIE Na
Attack
Hai-quan
Turns to XIE Na at once
Go away
All chasing
Successful escape
You are out of the boundary
Just at the time
The three boys
jump out
WANG Yuan (Roy) is chasing tightly
Hai-quan
Retreat to
the corner
WANG Yuan (Roy), …
Shouting
WANG Yuan
WANG Yuan (Roy), here
Here
Take this one
Successful transfer
Na-na gave the candy to WANG Yuan (Roy)
Rescue him
Hustle
Quan ge
I'm coming
Protect the candy closely
Anxious
Leader
Hold on
Will Hai-quan guard the candy?
Anxious
Onlooking
Immersed in his own world
Leehom, catch him
Hurried
Leehom
catch them
Suddenly awakened
Snatch
XIE Na made the rescue
The time's pressed
Watching
Leader
Hold on
Don't touch him
TIME'S UP
From this round, we can find
that a man's strength is quite different with a woman's
Out of
breath
Is it?
But I think
Na-na is very magnanimous
and this is a tactic
The leader's tictic, right?
Tactic
Sacrifice for preserving the strength
Give the candy to strengthened player
In this round, Selina and Na-na are out
Farewell
Leader
Hold on
I tried my best
Fight for it
We have two left
Only two left
We have chances
Encouraging
Two versus three
Now there are five players left in the field
In this round, there are
3 red candies
Five to three
5 players
3 candies
Sticking out
the toughe
Under
great pressure
But I find that the three boys
are very good at physical strength
The boys are plotting the tactic
One candy for each of them, and we win
Yes
Fighting
Do you have any tactic for this round?
Our tactic is
to huddle together after we get the candies
Excellent tactic
Huddle together
To huddle
We should
be aware
To huddle together after we get the candies
To crowd into a globe
Yes
Why do you say it out
Why do you say it out?
Too late
We have
known it
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Poised for the battle
Fighting, …
We have advantage in height
Who will win
Wait and
see
Candies eject
Jackson
Roy
Leehom
Karry
hold Hai-quan tightly
Doesn't snatch the candy
What's that tactic?
Our tactic is
to huddle together after we get the candies
Excellent tactic
Huddle together
But only huddled on Hai-quan's body
Never let go
Turns to
a koala
Cheered up
Well done
WANG Jun-kai(Karry)'s tactic
I'm fooled!
Their tactic is too bad
Hai-quan's armored footrace
Good chance
Leehom ge
is not defending
Innocent Leehom
Becomes Karry's target
Target changed
Dodged
Anxious
The time's pressed
Protect him
Protect Leehom
Hold
tight
Watch out
In the last seconds
Hai-quan holds the two tightly
TIME'S UP
Pitiful
Leader
is out
I think your tactic is great
But it's totally different from the tactic
you told me
That's the camouflage
Smart
Camouflage
Clever
We are
exhausted
You did a good job
It's too hard
Consoling
Leader, you did your best
You are great
Their tactic is too powerful
Their tactic worked
That's a good tactic
Now, Leehom, you are the representative of our team
the last hope
The last hope of Hai-quan's team
the last hope of the team
OK
It all depends on you
Like this …
Plotting new tactic
Got it
Leehom will show
the power as a hero of Earth
The next round is
three to two
3 players
2 candies
WANG Yuan (Roy), Qian-xi (Jackson)
WANG Yuan
Qian-xi
Reluctant to lag behind
Leehom, the most pop
Leehom
The most pop
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Candies eject
Leehom tripped
Fell in the final effort
Excellent chance
Slipped out
Catch him
Leehom
Leehom, catch him
Transfer
Leehom
Missed another chance
Leehom, fighting
Catch him, …
Catch it
Two boys cooperate perfectly
Leehom, go for it
Anxious
No
Leehom, go for it
Go, …
That's a good tactic
Excellent tactic
One person specially hinders Leehom
Look, …
He's locked
Out of
breath
Catch
Another perfect cooperation
Excellent
Converging attack
Will the result of this round
lead to the final battle of one on one
or the sifting out of Leehom?
[Sponsors]
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Will the result of this round
lead to the final battle of one on one
or the sifting out of Leehom?
Fighting alone
Leehom is gradually exhaused
Leehom, the most pop
A turnaround
Got you
Perturbed
Hold on
Throw
Tired
Leehom ge
Come and get it
Being dragged
Longing but can't get it
Tight defense
Koala
No. 2
Sorry
I'll
take it
TIME'S UP
Too pitiful
In this section, the last player in the field is
YI Yang-qian-xi (Jackson)
All the players, please get to the stage
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Leehom did a very good job
Nice
Well, who's the most tired among us?
That's Leehom
Yes
Indeed
He fight to the end
Really
All of you did a good job
It's showing the power of a team
Teamwork brings infinite power
Like TFBOYS
It's the power of a team
The most important thing is cooperation
and sacrifice oneself at critical moment
to help the teammate
Yes
Good
The tactic …
The tactic is very good
That's a successful tactic
In this section, Na-na's team wins
Invulnerable tactic
XIE Na's team wins
OK
Look at Na-na's contented looks
she knows for sure
that she gets the golden dice
How many volumes will they get?
Let's welcome the Super Girl
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Round 1
Round 2
Thank you
We can win
OK. We roll first
Fighting
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Round 1
Round 2
Roll a 50
What score will they get?
[Sponsors]
[Public weal plan]
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Round 1
Round 2
We roll first
Classical idols            New-gen idols
Roll a 50
What score will they get?
Got zero in Round 3
Cannot believe it
The temperature dropped to the freezing point
How can it be?
How can it be zero?
"Silver", how can it be zero?
Dear me
How miserable
What a bad luck
It …
I don't comply
Limp
Tell me
it's not true
What will be the number on the golden dice?
On tiptoe
Will the Lady Luck patronise XIE Na's team?
Fantastic!
Look up and sigh
In rapture
Festive air
XIE Na's team
Hai-quan's team
Round 1
Round 2
Round 3
It's too dramatic
Dear me
Classical idols            New-gen idols
All the efforts were in vain
That's too much
Wait
It's too dramatic
Let's take a photo, OK?
Ella suggests
Take a photo of the dramatic scene
Come on
Please take a photo for us
It's really rare
Take a photo
The final winner
is the new-generation
Why are we in such a bad luck?
top popular idol team
[Ad]
TFBOYS' show is to come
Speaking the Truth Is Daring
Performer
Stage Director
Choreographer
Dancer
XIA Zhen
SDT
TFBOYS' new song
Speaking the Truth Is Daring
[Rough translation]
Why do you like dog?
Why do you empty your mind?
Are you thinking of a girl with black long hair
who take you away?
Fight in the game overnight
The dark circles are expanding
It's horrible to stay up late. Wash yourself and go to bed
The spider is on your back
your scared look is like a fool
Don't show off your poses
The table manner's ugly. You are too narcissistic
You can leave the checkout even without paying the bill
it's because I'm behind you
Speaking the truth is daring
But you don't have to pretend in front of me
Just laugh as you want. It's okay to go too far
But please save my face in front of girls
Speaking the truth is daring
for you know all my merits and faults
When happy, I just wanna show
When angry, I just wanna go
[Source: 十年一顾杂货铺]
But you understand me. And that is enough
[Translation: Quadrifolium]
[Timing: Quadrifolium]
[Encoding: Quadrifolium]
Hello. Bye-bye