No.
[Translation: Quadrifolium]
I Am Your
TF Phone
WANG Jun-kai
(Karry)
WANG Yuan
(Roy)
YI Yang-qian-xi
(Jackson)
V-Lian Shezhang Studio
Mum
Hi, mum
At home
Go out? Where to go?
I like staying in my room
Too many people and too many cars are outside
I don't want to go out
I don't need any friend
I can have a good time alone
Fine. Go out, … I will. Okay?
I Am Your
TF Phone
I'm sorry
Did I bump your eye?
It's nothing
Shall I ask for a doctor on the train?
I'm really sorry about that
Never mind
I was worried if something goes wrong
That's a nice guitar
Cool, huh?
Can you play guitar?
That's my seat
Sorry. I'm sorry
What do you two take the train for?
I? I'm on a trip
A trip? It's called "a journey"
What about you?
What are you doing?
I? Roaming
Roaming? What's your destination?
Poetry and the soul afar
A quote from GAO Xiao-song (高晓松).
Zhong er [delusive]
"Zhong er bing"(中二病, ちゅうにびょう): hebephrenia, or adolescent delusions.
As a man in anime shirt
who's more zhong er [delusive]?
Hey, kids. Do you have OPPO?
My phone's out of charge
May I borrow your VOOC Flash Charger?
Just 5 minutes
"Kids"? Who's a kid?
Exactly
I'm taller than him
I'm now fifteen, but have to be called a "kid"
What a coincidence. I'm also fifteen
Excuse me, kids
I'm sixteen
But you are reading the same anime as me
Haven't you said it's zhong er [delusive]?
I'm YI Yang-qian-xi
What's your name?
I'm WANG Yuan
And you, zhong er bing [delusion]?
I'm WANG Jun-kai, roamer
Hey
Why are you here?
Isn't here a famous resort?
And you get off here, too
I'm here to rob. Where's your money?
My wallet?
You lost your wallet on the train. Are you really sixteen?
Is this the first time you are out alone?
WANG Yuan
WANG Jun-kai said he'll treat us for dinner
Did I?
Why should I treat you two for dinner?
I'll search if there's something tasty
There's a Chicken House nearby
Really?
Fried chicken is my favourite
Go
WANG Yuan
Help me to play the music
My fingers are greasy
Qian-xi
It's out of charge. Can I charge it for you?
Please do it
Mm
Flowers
Look
Deep ocean, my hometown
Hey, how about a running race here?
Let's see who's the fastest
OK
Start
Aiya, run
Long live the youth
Where shall we go next?
It's getting darker
Where do you want to go?
Is Clover Forest near here?
The fireflies there are quite famous
The scenery was on Hot Weibo Chart these days
How about taking a look?
Is there anything good about fireflies?
Just glowing bees
Search
Firefly, belongs to the order Coleoptera
is an insect which produces bioluminescence
Terrestrial fireflies generally inhabit places elusive,
lushly forested, and highly humid
Aquatic Fireflies requires stricter environment
with no water pollution and light pollution
Aiya, in short, it requires lush vegetation and plentiful water
But, fireflies appeared in Clover Forest?
It's strange
Anyway, the photos on the web are beautiful
Let's go and take a look
WANG Jun-kai, you are expecting, too. Right?
All right. Now that you are longing, it's fine for me
Just "fine"? You must
Go
Wait
Traffic Accident
An accident happened in the tunnel. The road is closed
Closed?
How can it be possible? Everything went well on our way here
We still have time if we go back now
But if we keep going
we have to stay on this mountain overnight
Maybe we should go back
Since you said fireflies are just glowing bees
I hate giving up halfway
You may leave if you want
I can get there on my own
Co-presented
The right of propagation of this video on the Internet
belongs to Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.